There's an old joke, um.
Two elderly women are at a
Catskill mountain resort,
and one of 'em says, "Boy, the food
at this place is really terrible."
The other one says, "Yeah, I
know; and such small portions."
Well, that's essentially
how I feel about life
full of loneliness, and misery,
and suffering, and unhappiness,
and it's all over
much too quickly.
The other important
joke for me,
is one that's usually
attributed to Groucho Marx
but I think it originally
appears in Freud's
"Wit and it's Relation
to the Unconcious"
and it goes like this
(I'm paraphrasing):
"I would never want to
belong to any club
that would have someone
like me for a member."
It's the key joke of my adult life in
terms of my relationships with women.
You know, lately the strangest things
have been going through my mind, cause
I turned 40, and I guess I've been going
through a life crisis or something
And I'm not worried about aging, you
know, I'm not one of those characters
Although, I'm balding slightly on top,
that's the worst you can say about me
I, um, I think I'm going to
get better as I get older
You know, I think I'm going to be
the, the "balding virile" type
As opposed to, say, the, um,
"distinguished grey", for instance
Unless I'm neither
of those two
Unless I'm one of those guys with
saliva dribbling out of his mouth
who wanders into a cafeteria with a
shopping bag screaming about socialism.
Annie and I broke up, and I still can't
get my mind around that, you know
I keep sifting the pieces of the relationship
through my mind and examining my life
and trying to figure out "Where
did the screw-up come?" you know?
A year ago we were in love,
you know? And, and -
It's funny - I'm not a morose type. I'm
not a depressive character.  I, uh,
I was a reasonably happy kid, I guess, I was
brought up in Brooklyn during World War II.